this is the time known as the great pirate era a countless array of pirates go to battle across
the seas in search of the one piece the legendary treasure left behind by gold roger king of the
pirates monkey d luffy a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit set sail
to become the next king of the pirates as luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles they
capture the unwanted attention of the world government which will use any means necessary
to stop them now this is exciting i can't wait to see what kind of adventures up next
with a charted course awash in danger and intrigue the crew will cover path across the grand line
to the new world after losing his brother ace in the war of the best against the navy
luffy comes face to face with dark king rayleigh well then that's it meanwhile the rest of the
straw hats are in a hurry to reunite to keep the promise they made to each other and their captain
okay i've made up my mind if you think i should i'll go back to marine ford
a disaster for sanji the queen's return to the kingdom
this is navy ship number 204 requesting permission to enter urgently you're right on time i just need
your code number and i'll get you through yes that would be five nine six three all right code number
confirmed open the gate of justice sir well done young man luffy are you starting to feel better now
yep doesn't hurt at all anymore good as new man the warlord jinbei the one they call the first son of
the sea with the former first mate of the king of the pirates dark king silvers rayleigh
and straw hat luffy too what could they be after
meanwhile in birdie kingdom where the birds and the humans have finally reached an agreement
we not long ago make friends raccoon really leave now
yeah as soon as i read that newspaper and found out what my friends been going through
i realized i couldn't stick around any longer
i had just met luffy's brother in alabaster i can't believe what happened to him
i'm worried about luffy what if he needs medical attention he always pushes himself way too hard
good friend anyway it's good to see you and the birds are getting along better now
understanding only happened because brave raccoon friend risking life to do talking
aww you guys remember not to pick fights with the humans okay
they're not gonna hurt you they just want you to let them pick the plants that grow on that tree
raccoon speaking truth we no fight you are taking eggs
we not same as bad humans that stealing your treasure and chase you away we are friends
oh by the way i was really impressed with that medicine you guys gave me when i got injured before
it's great stuff see i'm better already right we using special medicine recipe we passing down over many
generation to tell you the truth i wish i could stay here with you guys and study those plants for a
while i'm sure there's still a lot i could learn but the timing's kind of bad right now come back soon
okay not right you always welcome here raccoon
really that makes me so happy after my friends and i find each other i'll tell them all about this
amazing place i found and i promise when i can i'll come back and visit okay take journey long maybe get
hungry oh wow thanks see raccoon soon
hey i love cotton candy
so long everybody be nice to each other
goodbye raccoon you travel safe now that i've got a yummy lunch and all the cotton candy i can eat
i'm ready to head for the meeting spot so i can help luffy
wait i just realized i don't have a pirate ship and even if i did i don't have a navigator
how am i supposed to make it to sabote if i don't even know the way it's okay i'll just get on
any ship i can find no then they might take me someplace weird also what ships where what was i
thinking he big dummy so pirate i am i can't even make it to sea sorry loopy
what what did you say your papa can fly me there hey that's an awesome idea
lucky me why didn't i think of this in the first place i'll be there no time flat you're so fast mr
bird what what you can go faster but
cool
it's just like a roller coaster
i can read this while i have my lunch they should have some new info about the war by now
what that's crazy
no way i don't believe it luffy what's going on
what's going on
meanwhile in the east blue now that robin has been freed by the revolutionary army
i'm so happy robin oh we're all safe this means everybody will
be free from now on right yes
at the very least you won't be forced to work on that awful bridge anymore
hey um i hope you like this
soren thanks
you're leaving now
yes
robin
will you be back
one question
you're headed for saba odin now aren't you
i am
the light of revolution
for 10 years we have been searching and that's what we've called you it's quite suitable i think
you're the only survivor from ohara the brave country that fought against the whole world
and now that we've finally found you we will shield you from the government at all costs
those are our bosses orders
boss
the leader of our army dragon
luffy's father
fate is strange sometimes
once again i implore you would you please let us introduce you to our boss i'll take you to him
myself
i can't
there's somewhere i have to return to immediately
besides i don't need you to look out for me
after all i have my friends
i assume you're talking about the straw hat pirates
yes
then at least let us carry you part of the way
the bridge we're on it's incredibly long you can walk for days and not see the end i insist
wherever you're going let us help you sorry to interrupt sir but i have good news
it looks like we'll be able to unlock the third and fourth prisons before much longer
roger that in the meantime make sure we have a team ready in case they're injured or confused
sir please tell me something absolutely it's about your army you seem to need me and i would like
to know why all right then
between here and the end of the bridge you'll notice a lot of ghost towns
that's because the whole country relocated while the construction was going on
for example that one there is from 300 years ago
then why would they keep building as always because the world nobles ordered it
i see but honestly the reasons don't matter that doesn't justify the deaths of those who've been
enslaved here it's all the same
hey dragon's kid straw hat luffy was in the newspaper today did you see it yeah he's nuts
goes missing after the war then pops up again to do something crazy like this
either way we should show this article to nico robin as soon as we can
she's been worried sick about straw hat sure but i don't think they've made it to the end of the
bridge yet oh thanks for the newspaper this is for you luffy oh good he's safe
what is everything all right hard to tell whether you're shocked or amused over there
both
so
Now we take you to Kamabaka Kingdom,
a pastel-colored paradise on Peachy Island
where the newcomers reside.
Come on! Really? I told you to give me a ship!
I have a promise I'm supposed to keep, damn it!
There's no time for me to goof around with you guys anymore, all right?
Try a bit harder, candy boy.
That's obviously an excuse to escape this island.
We're not letting you go.
So what if it is an excuse? I'll come right out and say it.
If I don't see some pretty girls, I'm gonna shrivel up and die.
In case you haven't noticed, this isn't my scene.
Could that be who I think it is?
Oh my god, it is! Queen Eva is on that boat!
Huh? Why do we care?
Jeez, control yourself.
Whoever he is can't be that special.
She is the ruler of our kingdom!
Queen Emporio Ivankov!
Ivankov? Hold up.
That's the queen I read about in the paper. Talk about good timing. She was traveling with Lupi, so she's gotta know something useful about him.
Ah, home sweet home.
Whoa, it's my lucky day.
What a body!
No, I can't.
She's totally a dude under all that hotness, otherwise she wouldn't be on this island! I'm not gonna fall for it!
Huh?
Hey there, you got a name?
Uh, I, uh...
Her boobs are a perfect ten! And her butt's nice and tight too!
No, you're not gonna win me over!
Is there anything I can do for you, candy boy?
Yeah, I've got a lot of questions for you, buddy, and the first one is...
Are you single?
I mean, it's about Luffy.
What? Luffy? You mean the cutie with the straw hat?
Bingo! Listen, I just read in the paper that you were busting heads with him at Marineford.
Oh, Luffy, you lucky bastard!
Anyway, you might know how he's doing, so I was hoping you would fill me in on that, baby.
Huh?
How? About?
No.
Oh man, and I saw it coming from a mile away too! Screw you!
Too bad! Now tell me, how do you know Straw Boy?
We're shipmates.
Huh? You're a part of his crew?
So, Straw Boy here is your captain.
Yeah, so?
Then you're friends with pirate hunter Zorro.
No!
And what about cat burglar Nami?
Are you familiar with the king of snipers pictured here?
Yep.
And this one is you?
Hell no!
You're not on any of these wanted posters, so you must be a fraud!
Sorry, but I have yet to see proof of your relationship with Straw Boy!
What do I have to do to convince you?
Tell me what you know about Luffy, you fishnet-wearing freak show!
Now!
It says right here in this newspaper that you were there with him!
So you admit this is you?
No, it's not!
I mean, kind of, but...
I'm Sanji, but I...
Gosh, this is a problem area for you, isn't it?
All right!
Fine!
It's me!
That hideous thing on the wanted poster is me!
You win!
Now!
Hm?
Nope.
No match.
But you still made me say it!
I was coughing up blood, you jerk!
Too bad for you.
Because if there's even an infinitesimal fraction of a chance that you're a puppet for the Navy or the government,
I won't be divulging one iota of the information I have about Straw Boy.
Certainly you can understand why.
Yeah, I get it.
At least let me borrow a ship.
I've got to get to the meeting spot as soon as I can!
No ship for you.
All right, then!
I'll start swimming!
Ah!
Such awesome dedication!
You were telling the truth when you said you were a member of his crew!
Well, in that case, I have no choice.
You moved me.
So out of respect for your undying devotion to Straw Boy, I'll tell you everything.
Or maybe not!
Hee-haw!
You had me going!
What a trickster!
You're so smart!
Nobody asked you, morons!
Damn it!
Oh, looks like his guard's down.
Nice!
Maybe we can get him into that darling dress for McClure!
Not even if you paid me!
Now back off!
Listen!
I'm a manly man who likes ladies!
Sexy ones!
Hear me?
And none of you creeps make the cut!
Boo!
Hey!
Eva, I think it was.
I decided since I'm a pirate, I'm gonna take your ship!
I challenge you to a duel!
All right.
And now, Queen Eva, the Grand Master of New Kamakenpo, will face Black-Legged Sanji in a three-minute winner-take-all match!
Judging by how strong his stand-in was, it's probably gonna be tough.
I gotta warn you, I won't hold back!
Fight!
Diable Jambes!
Premier Hodges!
My!
You're powerful!
I don't think I can resist!
I'm beginning to falter!
I do believe this is the end!
Here I go!
Yee-haw!
Aw, you got us again!
You're such a theater!
You appear to be a sturdy fellow, but I dare say you could benefit from some serious discipline.
What?
New Kamakenpo!
44th Aesthetic Technique!
I call it my hair removal fist!
Ah!
Death!
Wink!
Hell!
Ah!
Galaxy!
Wink!
Ah!
Very well, Mr. Curly Brows, I'll give you an update on Straw Boy.
So what made you change your tune all of a sudden?
Oh, please.
There's no need to hide what the whole world knows anyway.
What's going through that little guy's head, I wonder?
It's in today's paper?
Whoa!
You've got a call from Baltigo.
Oh?
The boss is waiting.
Please come with me.
Goodness.
Everyone seems to have learned a great deal about you since the war, haven't they, Dragon?
That must have been very upsetting for your men.
Huh.
Actually, they were happy to find out their mysterious boss didn't have a heart of stone after all.
Well, it doesn't make any difference now, does it?
Luffy's not a kid anymore.
Regardless, I was surprised to hear you were there with him.
Destiny sure works in interesting ways, huh?
As for myself, it's been one twist after another.
What with the prison break and meeting your little bundle of joy.
Needless to say, I have several questions to ask you.
I'm sure you do.
The time has come for us to call our commanders from every corner of the world as quickly as possible.
Now that Whitebeard is dead, the government, regime, and the world's situation are going to change.
Not only that, but it occurs to me I haven't gotten to tell you what happened to Kuma.
Yes, that certainly was a nasty surprise.
Working for the government is bad enough, but now robot clones?
I still can't believe he tried to do me in.
I suppose the Kuma we once knew is no more.
By the way, Dragon, have you seen today's news?
Strawboy's thrown me for a loop yet again.
He's just as wild as his father.
He seems to be relaying some kind of message.
And in Marineford, no less.
Although Navy Headquarters was left in ruins after the War of the Best,
Marines and reporters still stalk its grounds.
Luffy, Rayleigh, and Jinbei return to where Ace lost his life to carry out a mysterious plan.
The world is shocked.
But will Luffy's crew understand his actions?
On the next, One Piece!
Unexpected re-landing!
Luffy to Marineford!
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!
The Pirates!